[music]
to put on a show. Now I found a home.
I'm filling my soul
with devotion and stardust.
[singing and music]
I'm
[music]
>> [music and bell]
>> Oo,
[music]
baby. [singing]
Oh
yeah. [singing]
[music]
Oh
m
[music]
there's a heavy [music and singing]
weight you've been trying to hold on to.
But you can lay it [singing and music]
all down with me.
Cuz [music] in the end, I'm just trying
to show you,
[music] you don't need more pain than
misery.
And [music] baby, baby, baby, you got to
hold on to what we [music and singing]
got. And give me give me give me
all of your [singing] love.
>> All of your love.
>> Yeah. Baby, baby, [music] baby, you got
to [singing] hold on to what we got. And
[music] give me, give me, give me
all of your love.
>> All of your love. Cuz me [music] and
you,
we got a good thing going.
Don't cast it [singing] off.
Just let this love keep [music] showing.
Yeah.
[singing]
Ooh. [music]
Ooh.
[music]
You say you're [music] tired and you're
growing [singing] weary.
[music] I'm here to give [singing] you
everything you need.
Your heartaches and pain will
[music and singing] all heal with time.
Girl,
[music] your love is [singing] mine if
we plant the seed.
>> [music]
>> And baby, baby, baby, you got [music] to
hold on to what we got. And give me,
give me, give me [music]
all [singing] of your love.
>> All of your love. Yeah. Baby, [music]
baby, baby. You got to hold on to what
we got. [music] And give me, give me,
give me, give me all of your love.
>> All of your love. Oh.
Ooh. [music]
[bell]
[music]
I ain't afraid of the dark. [music]
Once you let the light in, you won't see
[music] the beautiful stars shining
[singing] down from afar.
No, I ain't [music] afraid of the
[singing] dark.
I [music] don't mind the rain.
Bringing life back. We can brea again
when dealing with the pain.
[music] No, I don't mind the rain.
And
that's the way [music and singing] it
goes. Life will teach you what you need
to know. And
like a river flows, life [music] will
take you where you where you need to go.
[singing and music] Don't bother me.
[music]
I want to
know getting old.
>> Truth can be a bit pill,
[music] but it'll do you right and set
you free the way a lie [singing] never
will. Like climbing up [music] the
steepest hill.
But truth can be a bit pill.
That's the way it [music] goes. Life
will teach you what you need to know.
It'll
like the river flows. Life will take
[music] you where you need to go.
Oh, it's so
[laughter]
funky.
Hey, welcome back to my YouTube channel.
If you're new here, my name is Wiki.
Welcome. And if you're a returning
subscriber,
I'm in the What is this thing called?
I'm just worried if a car comes. But
yeah, I'm heading out. I think I'm
having a good day.
So, um it was my helper's birthday like
this month. And then um today and then I
bought I asked her what food she like
and Sana I have the most gentle and
quiet helper ever and respectful. So she
was like no I'm fine. I have everything.
I'm okay. But I know then I had to do my
own investigation and I found something
that she needs and I got it for her. So
[snorts] today they delivered it. Um so
what are this checkers
big things you know um that
and then that and data comes like he's
old enough to be my father and then like
already
without even me saying anything he was
like oh I'm having a good Monday by the
way today is Thursday he's like I'm
having a good a great Monday I'm like
what do you I mean, we're having a great
Monday. It must be nice.
[snorts] And then, oh, he broke my
heart. He's like,
we saying I want his exact words, but
something like
and I'm like, what do you mean?
And then he continued, he's like, people
who have money, they don't treat us,
they don't treat people
or something like that. I'm like, like,
is it that bad?
The deliveries that I make, they even
allow their dogs to chase us, guys. And
then,
and then they'll be standing there
laughing.
>> [clears throat]
>> I'm like I was so shocked
and being kind.
Please be kind. Like
like imagine
even if they report at at work um they
just laugh at them. Oh no. Ha, you know
how llines are always right and stuff.
I'm like,
not even but people like that. And I was
so happy when I gave [clears throat] her
her gift. Oh, she was so happy. She was
so happy.
something. I'm like, "Oh,
so I think I'm having a great day
because
um I made people happy today, you know.
So, yeah, I just love seeing people
smile and I'm very I'm a I'm a very
intentional person and I like seeing
people happy. That's me. Very
intentional. Let me go. I have to go to
cuz I'm ying yippy yep yeping and
yeping. I have to go to
um Pa because I have to
fetch a pastel from sneaker boss and
then I want to go to
let me open in the the garage and I want
to go to my designer.
Yeah,
guys.
I forgot.
Plus, I needed something to bribe her
jacket and that he normally uses when he
studies and they're very comfortable.
[laughter]
He asked me so early today. Baby, please
take my jacket.
So because I'm going to her
bribe once, let me bribe her.
Tell me if I got it, [music]
but
you don't want to be alone.
spend the evening by yourself.
>> Guys, I'm here at
spa. I don't know what to cook today.
So, I'm here to check what can I cook?
That is quick. And yeah, and I have
dresses.
[laughter]
Let's see if I have money. But yeah, let
me go. I'll show you guys what I got.
[music and singing]
[music]
If you let go,
boy,
you don't have to play smart. [music] We
can take it slow. You know it.
Go ahead and tell your friends. [music]
Talk it out, but it won't end.
You are never true to heart.
[music and singing]
You need me when it's getting dark.
Got [music] it all.
>> All righty. unbag and we have a few
things to unbox. Firstly, we have
Sneaker Boss. So, in here it's another
FOS one because
[laughter]
F1 guys is really nice when it's new
like new new.
So enjoy
the one that I have. It's old.
You feel like I need a new one. Oh, and
a pair of socks.
[snorts] Super cute.
And it's ta
guys. It's so nice. [snorts] Oo, the
quality.
The quality.
I'll leave her number down below like um
Sneaker Boss. That's where I get most of
my sneakers. And then next we have these
two dresses. And sadly, I'm not going to
plug you guys because the lady also
could seat like we bought um these
dresses I think last month and they're
only coming now like literally and we
had to call all the time or text to ask
her.
So, [sighs]
and it's you who who plugged us with
this person. So, I'm not going to plug
you guys.
It's two dresses or one of those kind of
dresses or the ones that especially the
horses normally wear.
So, it's a dress. [snorts]
It's this brown one. It has touch of
orange. And then
this [clears throat] is the Duke.
[snorts]
And then it has this apron.
And [snorts] then we have the red one.
This is the apron. [snorts]
And this is the dress. [snorts] Um,
Dooku is somewhere in the plastic.
So yeah,
this is all we got. [snorts] And then
honey collector, these dresses,
you know, is selling Dara
Zara
leather jackets. So I took it
support and stuff.
It's black. Yeah, that's all I have, I
think. So thank you for I'm busy making
pork droters
and
yeah, I'm going to go pack everything
away then continue with Okay.
is busy studying and already on
[laughter]
[snorts] guys. He's saying I'm making
noises. So, I'll see you guys very soon.
And I think I'm going to go to the
bedroom and watch Big Brother.
Do you need anything?
>> Yes, baby.
>> Okay, my love.
[snorts] I'm forgetting something. So,
we also have this tracksuit
from Sneaker Boss. Um, I have it in baby
pink. Now we have it in butter yellow.
She also has it in chocolate brown,
red, blue, I think most of the colors.
It's so heavy. One thing about tuit
here, guys, it's really heavy. The
quality is really, really good.
>> [snorts]
>> This is the top. It's a three piece.
[snorts]
[snorts] And then we have the pants.
And they're really long. The pants
accommodate tall and short people.
Then
it has
sports bar
three piece.
So yeah,
here [music]
is [music] a safe [singing] card. You
don't have to play hard. love and let
go.
Boy,
you don't have to play smart. We can
take it [music] slow. You know it.
It's a blessing. And I know we can take
it [music] to the next level. If you let
go,
boy,
you don't have to play smart. [music] We
can take it slow. You know it.
>> [music]
[music]
>> If you let go,
boy, loving is a safe card. You don't
have to play hard. You love to let
[music] go,
boy. [singing]
You don't have to play smart. We can
take it slowless [music]
[music]
if you let go.
You don't have to play. [music]
[singing] We can take it slow.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Um, hi guys. Welcome back to my kitchen.
[laughter]
Um, I'm about to start with cooking.
Happy Sunday.
Not
like I felt like eating bri but because
maybe after the 10th of August [snorts]
things will go back to normal.
So yeah, but I'm gonna try to make
something
because the fire
pork rushes. I ordered wings, but the
order is only coming
5 to 6. So,
I'm not sure if I should wait for 5 to
60 um for the wings so that I can make
the whole shebam
vor pork rushes and some wings. Then I
was also thinking of making potatoes,
roasted potatoes.
Um and then I have to cook up obviously
if the roasted potatoes and I want to
make a quick salad. I don't think I have
everything for that salad, but I'm going
to use whatever that I have.
Vegetable achad cucumber and if I
remember I have peppers like all colors
of peppers and then I have cucumber. So
I guess
the only thing
this thing sweet chili. So I ordered
some leather checkers uh the whole
checkers thingy. If it's a lady then
it's fine. I will just add like sweet
chili fella. Then I know I'm done. So
for now we have to chop and chop and
chop and then spice the meat. Put it in
the oven and just wait. So yeah,
I have to listen to music since it's
Sunday and Sundays are for what are for
soul music. So I'm going to put on some
music and then maybe we will chat here
and there but mostly I just want to
listen to music and yeah so that I can
finish
but it's coming that order. So meaning
when the order comes but for now let's
spice up the meat chop chop
all of those things. So yeah
when you came over [singing and music]
my heart was on its way out.
I wasn't sober [singing]
and I was thinking [music] out loud.
I spoke of your bravery.
your wit and audacity
of coming over and letting [singing] go
of it all. [music]
Please
move
close [singing] to me.
You [music] love
dearly. [singing]
>> [music]
>> Move
close [singing]
to me.
Love [music] me
differently. [singing]
Differently.
[music]
You lay beside [singing and music]
me. You held my hand in the dark.
I started [singing] fighting cuz I was
scared of it all.
And isn't [singing]
it glorious [music]
how love gets the best of us?
Yeah, I got [music] feelings, but I'm a
[singing] tough one sometimes.
Please
move [music]
close [singing]
to me.
You
love [singing]
dearly
so
[music and singing] close to me and love
me.
Differently, [music and singing]
differently.
Please
move [music]
close to me. that [singing] you
love [music] dearly
so
[music]
close to me.
[singing] Love
me [music]
differently.
differently. [singing]
[music]
My head above the [singing] water.
Finally, I can breathe again.
Lost in the waves. I wonder, [singing]
but in your eyes I see no [music] pain.
You're a holiday, [music]
a break from the [singing] rain, sipping
your sunshine. Come [music] take me away
in the water.
Finally, I can [music] breathe [singing]
again.
You're a dream [singing] dream. Standing
[music] in your presence, carry me away.
Honey,
a dream [music and singing]
dream. Make me lose my senses. Carry me
[singing] away.
A dream [music] dream.
Come take me [singing] away.
I see a new horizon.
[music]
>> My two feet steady on the ground.
With you, I found my reason.
>> Yeah. To keep [music and singing]
chasing what we found.
You're a [music and singing] holiday.
A break from the rain. Sipping your
sunshine. [singing]
Come take [music] me away. No horizon.
[music] Finally, [singing] I can see
again.
You're a [music] dream. Dream, dream,
dream. [singing] Standing in your
presence, carry me away, honey.
I dream, dream, [music and singing]
dream, dream. I use my senses. Carry me
away, [singing] away.
[music] Dream, dream, dream.
Come take me away.
You're a dream, dream.
Standing in [music] your [singing]
presence, carry me away, honey. [music]
And dream, dream, [singing] dream,
dream. Make me lose my senses. Carry me
away. [singing]
A dream. [music]
Come take me away. My head above [music]
the water.
Finally, I can brea again. [music]
>> [music]
>> Blue dude
[singing]
kind of
shaded [music] by someone I'm [singing]
not really into.
Do you need to fix it?
Talking
It's [music] hard [singing]
to see you when your eyes look dull.
Who's going to [singing] save you?
Who's going to make you
not blue?
Not blue.
Sort of wy and jaded. But let's not
[music] talk about you.
You're song
on a rerun.
Are you hound dog tired singing all
night long?
Who's going to save you?
Who's going to make you
not blue?
Nothing.
[music]
Ooh.
Blue
moon.
Been one or two
since I ran into you.
Do you need [music] a picture?
It's hard to take one's [music] full.
Who's going to save you?
Who's going to be you?
Not you.
Guys, happy Monday. Um, [snorts] I'm
heading out taking aprons for
embroidery.
Yeah, somewhere here in the back. So,
yeah. And I thought by today
Yes. I thought by today the the TV stand
um process
would have started but Mugi needs the
the place to be quiet. So we're going to
have to wait until
um he's writing I think on Wednesday if
not Thursday and then that will then
that can start after after the writing.
So yeah,
I can't wait for him to finish with his
exams so that things can go back to
normal.
Hey boo.
Like
so yeah.
And then
um at least things are going to go back
to normal until
October. Then October he starts again.
[music]
>> [music]
>> She said I won't be back [singing]
in a while. Don't wait. Already packed
her bags, [music and singing] called the
cab, made space. And she said I won't
answer if you call [music] me when
you're lonely. I guess I let her go.
Never [music] mind. It's too late.
But I can't believe I let you think
about it seven days a week and this
[music]
end.
[singing]
[laughter]
And I also bought some McDonald's for
lunch. Actually, it's my breakfast and
lunch cuz I didn't have I didn't eat
today. So, yeah.
This is your girl. Um, I bought
but hey, I'll wear them the next day.
It's fine. I bought some boots. Go.
What's this?
Excuse me.
I forgot the name.
I love it. So, yeah,
I bought some boots. I also bought some
heels
and I also bought these other cute
shoes. They're so cute.
So, yeah.
And then yeah, mostly
and I got these other polka dots jean
pig clothing. I don't know polka dots.
I'm sure
very soon. They're so cute. They're
cream white with black polka dots.
So yeah, let me go in. I'm sure is
hungry if leftovers
lunch that I bought. I am back. So I
went to pick and bait clothing, Mr.
Prize,
she street and rage. That is the
name of the shop I was looking for. Um I
bought few things. I'm going to show you
guys.
For a surprise, I just got myself some
PJs.
They are gray and and pink. Baby pink.
Yeah, it's just a top and pants, your
regular PJs. And I think
yeah price tag
they 220
[snorts]
from range.
Oh, I got myself these heels.
Oh, super cute. I took size five because
I know during summer
during summer. So, I bought these.
They're so cute.
Yeah, they're in black. Super cute. In
size five. I think they were marked
down. Yes,
they were marked down to 175. from 250
to 175. [snorts]
And then
these are for kids.
Um
[snorts]
but is cute.
Um,
they're so difficult to open.
But I'll I'll just put a picture here
for you guys because if I remember
correctly, I took a picture of them.
[snorts]
Another bag.
But I'll still wear them next year. It's
fine. I just bought these ankle boots
because
our feet my my legs don't fit. So yeah,
I had to buy this ankle one. It was 300
[snorts]
3.95. So it was 400 rand basically. I
took size five
on my ankle. So I took this ankle boot.
Super cute.
[snorts]
And then from
Oh, I also went to Vini. [snorts]
This is from Pick and Paint Clothing. I
got these polka dot jeans.
They are folded like this. It's a
straight cut. [clears throat]
And I took size 18, size 18, size 42
because they're a bit stretchy.
And it was 330.
Yeah.
How am I going to style them? But
I know is.
And then
from Fushini, I just bought given this
um Lancome body mist. It trending
somewhere Tik Tok. I saw it somewhere on
Tik Tok and I was like, "Oh, I should
get it." So I got this. It was 400 and
something. I like this one.
And then this is the Fushini brand body
mist.
So I bought this one. This smells so
good. Oh, guys.
I hope ya. It was 500 something. And
this one it was
for I don't see the price, but yeah.
What else? Oh, and then from cheat
street, I got these other cute
containers.
I don't know what I'm going to um like
use them for as yet, but I do. Lastly,
from she
got these. I got two. One was 30 Roman.
They're so cute. I'm not sure as yet,
but yeah, they're really, really cute.
So, that's all I got today
and I'm just going to end this vlog
right here. I hope you guys did enjoy
it. Don't forget to give this video a
thumbs up,
comment, and subscribe if you haven't.
What are you waiting for?
So, yeah. [sighs]
Bye.
Hey, man.
Let me show you guys. I did. Oh, I think
I did
the leather jacket with those
type of vibe dresses that normally wear.
I think I showed you guys. Yeah, I did
last if I remember.
So, okay. Bye for now. And I don't know
what to do with my hair, but I do
suggest
I don't know. But I'm planning to to to
play back line straight back cuz yeah at
this point I'm tired of
of boing. So I want to do like maybe
straight back and it's a very simple
until I don't know. So yeah. Bye.